{
    "id": "6b807ffa97204fd8acdc7cbe77f8c3b4",
    "title": "Direct And Indirect Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Sam asked me ........................ I was going to the party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "that",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "aa3f43d99bd344e38c6612509a25ca3b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rajiv said that he ......................... something to eat.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "needed",
                "needs",
                "was needing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "794233d3da7946aea85a6898864605b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Martin said that he ....................... that party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "doesn't like",
                "didn't like",
                "hasn't liked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b7b2f99cd6b44a858ccaaa9f72199140"
        },
        {
            "question": "Salini asked where ...........................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was her bag",
                "her bag was"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ee5fee1c6e5c475baf0f213106cee87b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher told the boys ...................... quiet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to keeping",
                "keeping",
                "to keep"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ab82da91e7c14299a707937ac98e55c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Maria said that she ..................... to see the doctor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wants",
                "want",
                "wanted"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2381ac286a1349afa65a6e89cc88e5e2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sophia said that she ...................... apply for that job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "must",
                "had",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5c672b79045d4d76bced18ce2baaf033"
        },
        {
            "question": "The policeman asked the woman where .....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was she going",
                "she was going"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6dcc5045c85446f39754be254331dbac"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rahul asked me ...................... crying.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "why was I",
                "why I was"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "61fee329bbbd4264a266e5d5c20e1934"
        },
        {
            "question": "Suma told her mother that she .................. be working late that night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0e76f8bfcf314292a66ef8315ab299de"
        },
        {
            "question": "Manu asked his mother where ....................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was his key",
                "his key was"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e523873c1fdf4beb871662b614138692"
        },
        {
            "question": "The mother asked her son if he .................. his homework.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was finished",
                "has finished",
                "had finished"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5ad778ccddcf4d4eb8a4c7503a03d5cd"
        }
    ]
}